<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Masquerave Podcast</title><link>http://www.masquerave.cz/</link><description>Recent content on Masquerave Podcast</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 22:09:54 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://www.masquerave.cz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>#51 – PANDEMIC SPECIAL</title><link>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/51/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 22:09:54 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/51/</guid><description>The Masquerave podcast is back for a pandemic special episode! Z-Kat present some of the hottest Bandcamp Friday tunes from the last couple of years as well as a preview of his forthcoming MICROCOSMS EP, coming out on December 30 2021 only on Bandcamp.
Date: December 2021
Length: 1:02:40
Guest: None
Track List Nkom Bivoué – Zeun Ya Yop Hagan – Osh WZ x Magugu – Movin Sharp (Hypho dubplate flip) Tribal Brothers &amp;amp; DJ Polo – Bullet Rice Kaval – Leaf Cutter DJ Whitecoat – Bongodian DJ Polo, Tribal Brothers &amp;amp; Scratchclart – Cola Bottles Am Jams &amp;amp; Murder He Wrote feat.</description></item><item><title>#50 – THE RELEASE OF THE MONTH HALL OF FAME</title><link>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/50/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2019 22:10:09 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/50/</guid><description>The 50th and final (regular) episode of the Masquerave podcast brings you one tune from every Release of the Month, and of course two from this month&amp;rsquo;s. Taking you on a journey through bass house, uk garage, uk funky, grime, dubstep, bassline, 4x4, mutant bass, whistle bass, death electro and more.
This episode goes out to all the people who have come on the show as a guest, all the record labels who are still keeping it real, all the producers making sick tunes, and last but not least all the Masquerave listeners.</description></item><item><title>#49 – 2018 IN REVIEW</title><link>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/49/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Dec 2018 01:13:57 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/49/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s time to round up and whack out the very best tunes of 2018, and here they are! Brought to you by Z-Kat.
Date: December 2018
Length: 1:27:29
Guest: None
Release of the month: Phatworld – One Hundred EP [Off Me Nut]
Track List Nekst – Connections (Tuff Culture remix) Exit99 – Ravers Rob Freeman &amp;amp; Duck Key – Original Soundboy TS7 – Motion Shift (AC Slater remix) Axel Boy – Hurt No More WATSN – 123UH Petey Clicks – Club Heads Corrupt – The Loot Indox – Hold You Botnek &amp;amp; Aylen – Future of the Underground (extended mix) Daze Prism – 2005 (Nuaura remix) TSVI – Pull Up Aaee – Shots Kastle – In My Mind (Leda Stray remix) Roska – Feeline (Murder He Wrote remix) Leda Stray – Astray Snow &amp;amp; Murder He Wrote – TBC King Hydra – Fatality (Killjoy remix) Killjoy – Gangrene Pelikann x Tik&amp;amp;Borrow – Giv a Fuk Daze Prism feat.</description></item><item><title>#48 – THE WHISTLE BASS WORLD WAR 2014–18</title><link>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/48/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Nov 2018 01:13:53 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/48/</guid><description>This month after the round up of new tunes from the last month, it&amp;rsquo;s time for one last feature show. Nearly five years ago on New Years Eve I heard Superior Cornrows first EP on Off Me Nut Records and new from that moment whistle bass was the new sound. And it was! So this month&amp;rsquo;s feature show is a bunch of whistle bass tunes from the last 5 years. Turn up your woofers AND tweeters and don&amp;rsquo;t stop the hype.</description></item><item><title>#47 – NIGHTMARE EDITION</title><link>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/47/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 01:13:50 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/47/</guid><description>This month we bring you an especially relentless selection of tunes, slightly longer than usual, all from the last 31 days, from none other than Z-Kat.
Date: October 2018
Length: 53:48
Guest: None
Release of the month: Cajama – Exemption [Crucast]
Track List Onipa – Woza (Krywald Farrer remix) Populous – Caparica (Lorenzo BITW remix) Retrospect – Hoko Dub Kastle – In My Mind (Leda Stray remix) Vida Sunshyne – All Three Eyes (Murder He Wrote remix) Zed Bias &amp;amp; Trigga – Real Ryder Retrospect – Jewel Spectrum – Carnival Jack Beats – Roast Clean Shirt – U Got The Feeling France To UK – Creation Ralston – Mind Scan Axel Boy – Hurt No More Blame Illuminati – Selecta Dommix – Jungle Demon Pavv – Gangster Booda &amp;amp; Jamie Duggan – Introduction Cajama – Without You Cajama – Leave Me D.</description></item><item><title>#46 – FIDGET HOUSE NOSTALGIA EDITION</title><link>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/46/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Sep 2018 01:13:47 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/46/</guid><description>This month after all the best tunes of the last month, featuring a load of bass and snares and a couple of sick compilations, a Masquerave feature show takes you on a trip down memory lane to the late 2000s, when people still used MySpace, got music off blogs, and wobbly house music was cool.
Date: September 2018
Length: 1:13:12
Guest: None
Release of the month: Leda Stray – Astray [Tumble Audio]</description></item><item><title>#45 – THE SHORTEST EDITION EVER</title><link>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/45/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2018 01:13:44 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/45/</guid><description>This month, unfortunately, it&amp;rsquo;s the shortest show yet, where I take you through the top 12 tunes of the last month.
Date: August 2018
Length: 24:26
Guest: None
Release of the month: Dr Cryptic – Dahn Tahn EP [Chip Butty Records]
Track List Route 94 feat. Jess Glynne – My Love (Royal-T remix) Skue-K – Loco DJ Zinc – Dollars Albzzy – Contender Krissi B &amp;amp; Gater feat. April Ess – Blind Fineart – Lighter Crew VIP Mikey B – Warning Dr Cryptic – Rah Dr Cryptic – Wub DFB – In The Rave Nuaura – Tension Bass Adjustment feat.</description></item><item><title>#44 – GLOBAL WARMING EDITION FEAT. DJ ALYAZ</title><link>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/44/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 01:13:41 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/44/</guid><description>In this episode we present a guest mix full of weird and wonderful riddims from the man like DJ Alyaz, Sapyens Records boss and curator of the legendary DROPS compilations. This follows Z-Kat&amp;rsquo;s usual selection of the sickest tunes of the last month!
Date: July 2018
Length: 1:15:12
Guest: DJ Alyaz
Release of the month: Ozwald – Money Tree EP [Chow Down]
Track List (Z-Kat) CJ Reign – For Sure (Speed Garage mix) Phlegmatic Dogs – Cuatrocats NuBass &amp;amp; Deppz – Degenerate KSO/JG – Step Back (Tengu VIP) Champion – Run Dat Rico Tubbs – Trouble Shooter (Hadean remix) Sammy Virji – Punctuation Limita &amp;amp; Baadwrk – How U Doin Sekt 87 – Roller Sunday Roast – Ritual GUAU – G.</description></item><item><title>#43 – POOL PARTY EDITION</title><link>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/43/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2018 01:13:38 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/43/</guid><description>This month we bring you a round-up of the best tunes of the last month presented by Z-Kat. Several strong compilations make for a wholesome summertime selection of funky, bassline and garage.
Date: June 2018
Length: 55:18
Guest: None
Release of the month: Exit99 – Ravers [Tumble Audio]
Track List Jimmy Le Mac – Blue Tongue Motu – Anytime Theme DJ Nightmare &amp;amp; Bosh – Standard Banger Spookz &amp;amp; Dryman – Funky Bass Jook 10 – Hideout Far From Perfect – Misty Tengu – Right To Kill Botnek &amp;amp; Aylen – Future of the Underground DJ Zinc &amp;amp; Jay Robinson feat.</description></item><item><title>#42 – MEANING OF LIFE EDITION FEAT. DANKA</title><link>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/42/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2018 01:13:30 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/42/</guid><description>What is the meaning of life? Some say 42, others say gully riddims full of filthy bass. Z-Kat has plenty of that in his roundup of the tunes of the last month, which is followed by a long-awaited guest mix from Danka, with a slightly calmer and funkier groove to get you ready for the summer.
Date: May 2018
Length: 1:18:09
Guest: Danka
Release of the month: Petey Clicks – Club Heads EP [Night Bass]</description></item><item><title>#41 FEAT. DJ TUCO</title><link>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/41/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 01:13:27 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/41/</guid><description>This month Z-Kat and DJ Tuco take it back to back for an hour and a half from exile in Music Club Jižák.
With apologies for the recording quality.
Date: April 2018
Length: 1:33:02
Guest: DJ Tuco
Release of the month: Sekt 87 – Soundboy EP [Influx Audio]
Track List Florentino – Seductora Freak de l&amp;rsquo;Afrique – Akom (DJ Satelite remix) Syn &amp;amp; Doubt – Hollow L Vis 1990 feat. Mista Silva – Do My Ting Lorenzo BITW – Rio Grande DJ Dats – Wants To Feel Seb Zito – I Like It Scott Diaz – Back For The First Time Warren Paul – Love The Way Arthur D&amp;rsquo;Amour – Pornhub (CTRL A remix) Syn &amp;amp; TenTwentySeven – Dysphoria Bad Bunny – Krippy Kush (Maieli remix) Otm Shank – Kaida (Ahadadream remix) Tombstone1899 – Night Shift Skelecta – On The Block Sunday Roast – Sheeba Phlegmatic Dogs – Keepmastic VIP Bushbaby – Sacrifice Disperto Certain – Disabled Fork Knife &amp;amp; Tigs – Bring Your Crew Too Late Productions feat.</description></item><item><title>#40 – ELECTROSTIMULATION SPECIAL</title><link>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/40/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Mar 2018 01:13:24 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/40/</guid><description>This month after all the best tunes of March 2018, we take you on a gritty, pulsating trip down memory lane through the works of Z-Kat and Kanji Kinetic&amp;rsquo;s old label Electrostimulation Records, which would be 10 years old this month. Never forget your roots and don&amp;rsquo;t ever stop the hype!
Date: March 2018
Length: 1:09:52
Guest: none
Release of the month: Killjoy – Delusions EP [Tumble Audio]
Track List Kachina – What Kind [Affectionate Grooves] AC Slater – Amen Tribe [Night Bass] Fearz – Check It Out [Top Billin] Kyle Riot – Through My Eyes [YosH] Watsn – 123UH [Influx Audio] Crazy Cousinz – You Got Me [Nostalgic] AAEE/Bandi – Switchblade [More Time] Killjoy – Club Fade 95 [Tumble Audio] Killjoy – Gangrene [Tumble Audio] King Hydra – Fatality (Killjoy remix) [Project Allout] Pelikann x Tik &amp;amp; Borrow – Giv a Fuk [Influx Audio] R1 Ryders – On Your Marks [Current] Jook 10 – Fire [Roska Kicks &amp;amp; Snares] Bassboy – Fire [Crucast] Bushbaby – Fire [Maraki] Zenji &amp;amp; Sample Junkie – Beast Quest [Influx Audio] Docka – Sly Riddim [M62] Daze Prism – 2005 (Nuaura remix) [Articulate] Casement – Sophie Riddim [Top Billin] Blnd!</description></item><item><title>#39 – HISTRIONICS EDITION FEAT. TEA TRALNA</title><link>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/39/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2018 01:13:20 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/39/</guid><description>This month we bring you an exclusive guestmix from Bratislava&amp;rsquo;s very own Tea Tralna which takes you on a slow but fulfilling journey through various flavours of club music with impeccable technical precision! And that comes, as ever, after Z-Kat&amp;rsquo;s usual round up of the illest riddims of this rather frigid buffer month.​
Date: February 2018
Length: 1:13:50
Guest: Tea Tralna
Release of the month: Baadwrk – Outer Space EP [Chip Butty]</description></item><item><title>#38 – NO RULES EDITION FEAT. UNKNXWN</title><link>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/38/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2018 01:13:17 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/38/</guid><description>This month&amp;rsquo;s selection of tunes from Z-Kat is not what it usually is! Less bassline and more of a mixed bag, and all to hype a whole bunch of new parties coming up in Prague over the next month including appearances from Dehousy, Luru and Maya Jane Coles, and the inaugural Garage Rave night at FAMU on February 9th, for which we&amp;rsquo;ve got a weird and wonderful guestmix from Unizone boss UNKNXWN.</description></item><item><title>#37 – 2017 IN REVIEW</title><link>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/37/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2017 01:13:14 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/37/</guid><description>Z-Kat&amp;rsquo;s round-up of 2017 contains, as you would expect, plenty of bass and plenty of snares. It&amp;rsquo;s been a fine year.
PF 2018!
Date: December 2017
Length: 1:45:56
Guest: none
Release of the month: Daze Prism – Shipwreck EP [Four40]
Track List Tuff Culture – I&amp;rsquo;m Gonna [Four40] Francois &amp;amp; Louis Benton – Vader [Four40] Sinden &amp;amp; DJ Q – The Original [Night Bass] Jack Beats – Modulate [Night Bass] Vellum feat.</description></item><item><title>#36 FEAT. SAMPLE JUNKIE</title><link>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/36/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2017 01:13:11 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/36/</guid><description>To round up our third year of podcasts we bring you a banging guest mix from Mutant Bass veteran Sample Junkie, right after Z-Kat&amp;rsquo;s usual round up of the best tunes of the last month.
Date: November 2017
Length: 1:15:04
Guest: Sample Junkie
Release of the month: Sekt 87 – Gangster EP [Chip Butty]
Track List (Z-Kat) Wax Motif &amp;amp; Ricci – Foresaken Phlegmatic Dogs – Gotta Move Vellum feat. MC Vapour – Swivel Jay Robinson &amp;amp; GAWP – Oblivious DJ Madd – Badman Talkin (Murder He Wrote remix) Killjoy – Banzai Champion – Lighter VIP TC4 – Original Don Royal T – Come My Way Francois &amp;amp; Louis Benton – Jungle Demon Pavv feat.</description></item><item><title>#35 – UPSIDE DOWN EDITION FEAT. DETRIVORE</title><link>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/35/</link><pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 01:13:07 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/35/</guid><description>This month we bring you a short but sweet guest mix from Detrivore, who laid down a selection of her own productions for us just before tearing up Cross Club along with Sample Junkie at the last Masquerave vs. Funk&amp;rsquo;d Up night! And that comes, as ever, after Z-Kat&amp;rsquo;s round up of the best tunes of the last month.
Date: October 2017
Length: 1:01:05
Guest: Detrivore
Release of the month: Daze Prism – Flux LP [Project Allout]</description></item><item><title>#34 – SAUNA EDITION FEAT. STIFLER SELECTA</title><link>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/34/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2017 01:13:03 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/34/</guid><description>This month we have a lot to get hyped about! To warm up for another Masquerave vs. Funk&amp;rsquo;d Up night at Cross Club, z-Kat brings his round-up of the dirtiest and heaviest bangers of the last month, and to warm up for the inaugural REWIND party which will feature a rare appearance from the Dubsteblog DJs we bring you a short guest mix from their head honcho, Stifler Selecta.​
Date: September 2017</description></item><item><title>#33 – LETNÍ PIVO EDITION</title><link>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/33/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 01:13:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/33/</guid><description>To end the summer we simply bring you all the best tunes of the last month, presented by Z-Kat.
Date: August 2017
Length: 1:00:05
Guest: none
Release of the month: DJ Zinc – Full House [Bingo Beats]
Track List Wesley Jay – Took My Love (Wesley Jay &amp;amp; Danny Blaze Lick) [Digital Candy] Angelz feat. Hanz Gable – Supafly [Confession] Kendoll – Strange Tings [Four40] Jack Beats – Modulate [Night Bass] DJ Zinc – Push It [Bingo Beats] DJ Zinc – Gammy Elbow [Bingo Beats] DJ Zinc – Interbass [Bingo Beats] Motu feat.</description></item><item><title>#32 - HEATWAVE EDITION FEAT. MR. BE</title><link>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/32/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2017 01:12:56 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/32/</guid><description>This month we bring you an absolutely mental guest mix from Příbram&amp;rsquo;s #1 roadman Mr. Be, which takes the form of a whirlwind of 30 tunes in 45 minutes, packed full of bass and energy, following Z-Kat&amp;rsquo;s round up of the hottest tunes of the last month.
Date: July 2017
Length: 1:22:30
Guest: Mr. Be
Release of the month: Francois &amp;amp; Louis Benton – The Tournament / Vader [Four40]
Track List (Z-Kat) Rogue &amp;amp; Danny Foster feat.</description></item><item><title>#31 – Z-KAT'S BIRTHDAY BONANZA EDITION</title><link>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/31/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2017 01:12:53 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/31/</guid><description>This month I am celebrating my thirtieth birthday and as such I have totally hijacked this podcast for myself! After taking you through the best tunes of the last month, I will show you what my 20s sounded like&amp;hellip; they were restless, they were insane, they were heavy!
Normal service resumes next month&amp;hellip;
Date: June 2017
Length: 1:32:22
Guest: none
Release of the month: Surreal – SpaceTek [Chip Butty]
Track List Wookie – Gallium (remaster) [ManChu] Murder He Wrote – Mono [Roska Kicks &amp;amp; Snares] Jus Now &amp;amp; Roska – Osiris [Roska Kicks &amp;amp; Snares] AC Slater &amp;amp; Shift K3y – Come Back [Night Bass] Hadean &amp;amp; Deadbeat – Supernova [Project Allout] Jaikea – Invisible [U Wot Blud] Surreal – Feeling [Chip Butty] Surreal – Loving Me [Chip Butty] Superior Cornrows – 007Hillz [Off Me Nut] J69 – Dizzle VIP [Influx Audio] P Jam feat.</description></item><item><title>#30 – TRINITY EDITION FEAT. MYA &amp; SBSTRD</title><link>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/30/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2017 01:12:50 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/30/</guid><description>To celebrate our 30th show, Z-Kat takes it back to back with Mya and SBSTRD for over an hour and a half.
Don&amp;rsquo;t ever stop the hype.
Date: May 2017
Length: 1:43:16
Guest: Mya &amp;amp; SBSTRD
Release of the month: Brent Kilner – Shots On The Scene [Second To None]
Track List EVA808 - Balmy Egoless - Bubble Beat Gramz - AJ tracy Flip Flako - Lyrebird Mungo&amp;rsquo;s Hi Fi &amp;amp; Joe Deamer - Rules of the Dance (Kahn Remix) ft.</description></item><item><title>#29 FEAT. ASPECT SELECTAH</title><link>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/29/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2017 01:12:46 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/29/</guid><description>This month we start off with Z-Kat&amp;rsquo;s round up of all the best tunes of April 2017, which features a lot of heavy UK bass material and some stuff from top compilations, including a Czech Juke/Footwork compilation just released on Heldenkellerz which gets a short showcase at the end. The show finishes with Project Bass head honcho DJ Aspect Selectah delivering a damaging guest mix of heavy hitting grime riddims.</description></item><item><title>#28 FEAT. BUDGIE SMUGGLA</title><link>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/28/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2017 01:12:43 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/28/</guid><description>Following on from last month&amp;rsquo;s impressive guest mix from Influx:Audio label owner Tik&amp;amp;Borrow, this month we bring you another from his partner-in-crime Budgie Smuggla, which showcases another load of forthcoming material on the Influx label as well as turning the heat up and complementing Z-Kat&amp;rsquo;s relatively chilled selection of the best tunes of March 2017.
Date: March 2017
Length: 1:26:59
Guest: Budgie Smuggla
Release of the month: Majora – Valbandon / Armor King [Roska Kicks &amp;amp; Snares]</description></item><item><title>#27 FEAT. TIK&amp;BORROW</title><link>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/27/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2017 01:12:40 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/27/</guid><description>This buffer month we bring you a high octane guest mix from Influx Audio label heads Tik&amp;amp;Borrow, featuring a fair amount of exclusive material, right after Z-Kat&amp;rsquo;s round up of the best tunes of the last 28 days.
Date: February 2017
Length: 1:17:54
Guest: Tik&amp;amp;Borrow
Release of the month: Hybrid Theory &amp;amp; Trilla – VIP Remixes EP [Four40]
Track List (Z-Kat) Gporn – Eclectic Kids (1043 remix) [Proud Runs Deep] Dismantle – Huntsman [GutterFunk] Dean Lyon – Zimba [RKS Dubs] Lorenzo BITW feat.</description></item><item><title>#26 – PAR JANUARY SALE VOLUME 2</title><link>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/26/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2017 01:12:37 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/26/</guid><description>Just like last January we&amp;rsquo;re kicking off the year with a feature of the best catch from Project Allout Records&amp;rsquo; mega compilation from December, Project Allout Volume 2, right after Z-Kat&amp;rsquo;s round up of all the best tunes of the last month.
Date: January 2017
Length: 51:42
Guest: none
Release of the month: Pelikann – Internal Blue Screen EP [Influx Audio]
Track List Cuplrate &amp;amp; Tru Fonix – Solarised [Saucy] Phlegmatic Dogs – Serious Frenkie [Night Bass] Libra – Get Licked (Sirmo remix) [WoNKed Bass] Vital Techniques feat.</description></item><item><title>#25 – 2016 IN REVIEW</title><link>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/25/</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2016 01:12:34 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/25/</guid><description>This year&amp;rsquo;s round up is nothing more and nothing less than a selection of 50 tunes chosen by Z-Kat, to remind you all that no matter what you think of 2016, it had a fine soundtrack. No talking, just music (the relevant soundbites have been added to the track list)
​PF 2017.
Date: December 2016
Length: 1:37:46
Guest: none
Release of the month: Dr Cryptic &amp;amp; Sammy Virji – Chips N Gravy EP [Chip Butty]</description></item><item><title>#24 – NORTHERN LIGHTS EDITION FEAT. WHATSMAN</title><link>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/24/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2016 01:12:31 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/24/</guid><description>To round up the second year of Masquerave podcasts we bring you a guestmix from a DJ and promoter who has made a few waves in the Czech Republic in 2016 – Whatsman, head of Litoměřice club night LNDN Calling, who delivers a devastating mix of 20 tunes in 28 minutes, following, of course, Z-Kat&amp;rsquo;s regular round up of this month&amp;rsquo;s drift net residue.
Date: November 2016
Length: 1:09:48
Guest: Whatsman</description></item><item><title>#23 – SPIRAL EDITION FEAT. DEGERMARK &amp; HØJERE</title><link>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/23/</link><pubDate>Sat, 29 Oct 2016 01:12:27 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/23/</guid><description>This month we bring you an absolute trip of a guest mix from Prague-based techno duo Degermark and Højere, which takes you back across the old waves of Acid Techno with some other surprises thrown in. All of this follows Z-Kat&amp;rsquo;s usual rounding up of the best tunes of the last 30 days.
Date: October 2016
Length: 1:29:04
Guest: Degermark &amp;amp; Højere
Release of the month: Fish – Square Waves EP [Tumble Audio]</description></item><item><title>#22 – PANELSTORY EDITION FEAT. KEWU</title><link>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/22/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2016 01:12:24 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/22/</guid><description>This month Z-Kat and Kewu take it back to back for an hour and twenty while in exile in DJ Lab in Jižní Město, mixing on three decks, which gives our guest space to mix in some classic grime acapellas and other interesting flavours to Z-Kat&amp;rsquo;s usual round-up of the best tunes of the last month.
Date: September 2016
Length: 1:20:50
Guest: Kewu
Release of the month: Dr Oscillator – RS Turbo [Chip Butty]</description></item><item><title>#21 – LENG VS. SAUCE</title><link>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/21/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2016 01:12:21 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/21/</guid><description>This month Z-Kat&amp;rsquo;s roundup of all the latest tunes of the last month is followed by an homage to two compilations from Project Allout and Saucy Records which have provided so much sick new music that we even had to postpone this month&amp;rsquo;s guest mix! In this month&amp;rsquo;s feature you will find no ovens and no condoms, just pure rawness.
Date: August 2016
Length: 1:14:35
Guest: none
Release of the month: Skyjuice – Dark n Funky [Inner City Dance]</description></item><item><title>#20 – PUSSYCLART SUMMER VIBES EDITION</title><link>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/20/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2016 01:12:19 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/20/</guid><description>For our 20th show we bring you nothing more but an extended round-up of the last month&amp;rsquo;s best tunes, which takes you from summer vibes to Finnish 2-step to Czech grime to the usual gully bass filth. Thanks to all Masqueravers for making 20 shows possible and here&amp;rsquo;s to many more!
Date: July 2016
Length: 1:13:42
Guest: none
Release of the month: Tuff Culture – Edification [Four40]
Track List Damien Lazarus – Sacred Dance (Gorgon City remix) [dub] Dots Per Inch – Electricity (Dennis Brooks remix) [136 Grad] Sunday Roast – Damp Mudd [Soulserious] Hostage – Last Breath [877] Tuff Culture – Solar [F2] Carpainter – Browser Crasher (Sinden remix) [Top Billin] Cheeky D – Disco [Immoral] Bean – Feel It Coming [Future Follower] Tengu &amp;amp; Karl Vincent – Kaifeng [U Wot Blud] Born Dirty – 6 Feet Deep [Night Bass] Tuff Culture – Asia [Four40] Tuff Culture – Midnight Safari [Four40] Doctor Nick – Hot Air (Wolfe remix) [NM Recordings] Jay Robinson – Fury [Night Bass] Underheadz – Ragga Trip [Greedy Beats] Deadbeat – Deep [Project Allout] Vital Techniques feat.</description></item><item><title>#19 – SAPYENS EDITION FEAT. SBSTRD</title><link>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/19/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2016 01:12:15 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/19/</guid><description>This month we bring you a live mix straight out of Masquerave HQ from the man like SBSTRD, who will be appearing alongside the Sapyens Records crew, Z-Kat and South London dubstep prodigy Loefah at Cross Club on July 2nd. This time we open with the guest mix for a change, and follow up with Z-Kat&amp;rsquo;s brutal round up of all the most obscene filth from the last month.
Date: June 2016</description></item><item><title>#18 – SERENETTI EDITION FEAT. NIKKI PRYKE</title><link>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/18/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2016 01:12:11 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/18/</guid><description>This month we bring you a more relaxed guest mix from Stockholm soul queen Nikki Pryke (formerly Nikkita Sthlm) who brings you an hour long mix of deep house and dub techno vibes which will take your mind on a trip through a dark forest, and who knows what you&amp;rsquo;ll find in there? At least an antidote, to wash off the filth from Z-Kat&amp;rsquo;s characteristically obscene roundup of the illest tunes of the last month.</description></item><item><title>#17 FEAT. THORPEY</title><link>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/17/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Apr 2016 01:12:06 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/17/</guid><description>This month we bring you possibly the most insane, clinical guestmix Masquerave has ever experienced, straight from Off Me Nut records veteran Thorpey, which he recorded specially for us at Masquerave HQ prior to his crushing debut in the Czech Republic at Cross Club at the Funk&amp;rsquo;d Up party on April 23rd. And of course, this comes straight after Z-Kat&amp;rsquo;s usual roundup of the hottest sounds of the last month.</description></item><item><title>#16 – SLEEPLESS NIGHTS EDITION FEAT. ABAB</title><link>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/16/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2016 01:12:03 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/16/</guid><description>This month we have a lot to celebrate! The first thing is the release of ABAB&amp;rsquo;s album &amp;ldquo;Sleepless Nights&amp;rdquo; which came out a few months ago so we&amp;rsquo;ve got a guest mix and interview from them at the end of the show. The second is our collaboration with Funk&amp;rsquo;d Up on 23 April at Cross Club which will see Off Me Nut Records OG Thorpey make his debut in the Czech Republic.</description></item><item><title>#15 FEAT. DJ DROP A CAT ON THE EQUIPMENT</title><link>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/15/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2016 01:12:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/15/</guid><description>In this &amp;ldquo;Extended Buffer Month&amp;rdquo; edition we bring you an absolutely thrilling, stomping guest mix from US West Coast mutant bass-head Dropacat a.k.a. DJ Drop A Cat On The Equipment (NiceOnes Crew), who delivers a devastating mix of UK bass and mutant electroclash. All after Z-Kat&amp;rsquo;s regular rounding up of the best catch from the last few weeks.
Date: February 2016
Length: 1:24:49
Guest: DJ Drop A Cat On The Equipment</description></item><item><title>#14 - THE KRAMPUS 5 JANUARY SALE</title><link>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/14/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2016 01:11:57 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/14/</guid><description>In the first podcast of 2016, Masquerave pays tribute to Project Allout Records and their Krampus 5 compilation which was released for free in December, and is utterly epic, both in proportions and in power! But not before going through a round-up of all the best new tunes from the grimmest month of the year.​
Date: January 2016
Length: 1:10:49
Guest: none
Release of the month: Sinden – Crystal Maze EP [Night Bass]</description></item><item><title>#13 - 2015 IN REVIEW &amp; A MIX FOR THE DECADE</title><link>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/13/</link><pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2015 16:19:54 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/13/</guid><description>2015 was the first year of the Masquerave podcast.
Let&amp;rsquo;s re-live it in this nostalgic 69 track mashup which also features a fair bit of new material from the last month!
Also featured in this mix is Z-Kat&amp;rsquo;s mix of the decade to celebrate 10 years of DJing and collecting music.
Date: December 2015
Length: 2:04:35
Guest: none
Release of the month: B Squared – Square Root EP [Second To None]</description></item><item><title>#12 FEAT. EVA PORATING</title><link>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/12/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2015 03:48:51 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/12/</guid><description>To round off a great first year of Masquerave podcasts, this month&amp;rsquo;s edition features another slight change of format! Radio 1 (CZ) resident Eva Porating goes back to back with Z-Kat for over an hour, as they both play a diverse selection of their favourite new music.
Date: November 2015
Length: 1:19:19
Guest: Eva Porating
Release of the month: Juzlo – Time To Get Grimey [Project Allout]
Track List K-Lone – Broke [Wisdom Teeth] Martyn – EP40 [Dolly] Bassboy – Keep The Vibe [Deeprot] Distro feat.</description></item><item><title>#11 - NIGHT EDITION FEAT. FLEIKA</title><link>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/11/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Oct 2015 21:45:48 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/11/</guid><description>This month we bring you something slightly different in the form of a guest mix! As an homage to the techno scene which has dominated Prague this year we bring you a 40 minute long guest mix from local DJ Fleika, which is best listened to with the lights off. All this, of course, after Z-Kat&amp;rsquo;s rounding up of all the best tunes from October 2015.​
Date: October 2015
Length: 1:36:22</description></item><item><title>#10 – GRIME BLITZ EDITION FEAT. C.MONTS</title><link>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/10/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2015 21:58:46 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/10/</guid><description>This month we present to you a new kind of guest on the show, Prague-based MC C.Monts who takes over the mic at the end and shows us his best bars over a flash of grime riddims played by Z-Kat! All after Z-Kat&amp;rsquo;s regular round up of the best tunes of the last month.​
Date: September 2015
Length: 59:39
Guest: C.Monts
Release of the month: Superior Cornrows – Dark City EP [Off Me Nut Records]</description></item><item><title>#9 – LAST OF THE SUMMER BASS</title><link>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/9/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2015 22:33:42 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/9/</guid><description>This month we bring you a simple helping of all the best tunes of the last month, presented by Z-Kat.
Date: August 2015
Length: 56:51
Guest: none
Release of the month: Roby Howler – Naney Club EP [Meanbucket]
Track List DJ Whitecoat – Ecstasy [Sun Tribe Terrace] Funkystepz – Copyright [Four40] Mr. Breaks – My Rules [Synthebeat] Hotfire – Dip That [Night Bass] Dr. Cryptic – Dirty Dot [Chip Butty] Dr.</description></item><item><title>#8 FEAT. DJ SPOOKZ</title><link>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/8/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Jul 2015 21:58:38 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/8/</guid><description>This month we present you this warmup set from London UK Funky veteran DJ Spookz to prepare you all for his debut set in the Czech Republic! His set takes you through bass, UK funky, garage and rave and you can catch more of the same at Funk&amp;rsquo;d Up at Cross on 31.7. His cutting edge 40 minute guest mix comes straight after Z-Kat&amp;rsquo;s usual pick of the litter from July 2015, which takes a resounding bassline flavour this month.</description></item><item><title>#7 FEAT. KEWU</title><link>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/7/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2015 23:33:34 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/7/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s a great pleasure to announce that in a joint venture with Temporal promotions, the first Masquerave party is coming to Prague just seven months after the launch of the podcast! On Friday July 3rd at Beats.PM lounge you can catch ABAB, MGDLN, Waved, Kewu and Z-Kat. And in this month&amp;rsquo;s show you can check out the latter two, Kewu bringing a guestmix of fresh ghetto sounds after Z-Kat&amp;rsquo;s usual spotlight of the best tunes of the past month.</description></item><item><title>#6 – MEANBUCKET BIRTHDAY EDITION FEAT. DJ TUCO</title><link>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/6/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2015 23:11:31 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/6/</guid><description>This month to celebrate the 5th anniversary of Prague-based global bass label MEANBUCKET MUSIC, we bring you a guest mix from their head honcho DJ Tuco, comprising 30 minutes of entirely his own production. This of course follows your monthly dose of purely new music from Z-Kat.
Date: May 2015
Length: 1:24:38
Guest: DJ Tuco
Release of the month: Placido Elmtree – Triangles EP [Meanbucket]
Track List Cranks - Union Ave [Safer At Night] Underheadz - Love Tonight [FukPop!</description></item><item><title>#5 – TROUBLE AND BASS IN MEMORIAM</title><link>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/5/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2015 08:06:28 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/5/</guid><description>This month on the Masquerave podcast I bring you all the newest, hottest tunes from April 2015 in the first part of the show, and in the second half of the show pay my tributes to New York label Trouble &amp;amp; Bass Records, who&amp;rsquo;ve been releasing music close to my heart since 2007 and have recently decided to burn out rather than fade away.​
Date: April 2015
Length: 1:30:27
Guest: none</description></item><item><title>#4 FEAT. WAVED</title><link>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/4/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2015 23:24:25 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/4/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m back from Bangface Weekender - I survived - and that 4 hour Off Me Nut takeover has sure left a mark on me and possibly on others too as this month&amp;rsquo;s stock of new music has been an absolute onslaught of bassline, mutant bass, UK funky and grime! In addition to all the sickest tunes of the last few weeks we bring you a guest mix from fellow English DJ and Prague resident Waved who brings you a nice blend of grime, techno and wavey rap beats.</description></item><item><title>#3 – BUMPER BUFFER MONTH EDITION</title><link>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/3/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Feb 2015 22:29:21 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/3/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s the end of the month again – the shortest month, in fact, and it&amp;rsquo;s been an absolutely wonderful month for new material. This edition of the Masquerave podcast takes you from bass house to UKF to grime to mutant bass to garage again to some more chilled progressive and electro vibes at the end. Aside from a few totally necessary deviations the tunes are all fresh from the past four weeks or forthcoming.</description></item><item><title>#2 FEAT. PENRAR</title><link>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jan 2015 18:42:18 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/2/</guid><description>In the first Masquerave podcast of 2015 I bring you not only the freshest tunes of the month of January, but also a guest mix from Wigan resident Penrar (Collision, Wigan Live Festival) who digs deep into his crates (at last minute notice) to bring a devastating selection during the second half of the show.
Date: January 2015
Length: 1:32:16
Guest: Penrar
Release of the month: Drone – Skengman Mode [Project Allout]</description></item><item><title>#1 - 2014 IN REVIEW</title><link>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/1/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2014 19:12:47 +0100</pubDate><guid>http://www.masquerave.cz/posts/1/</guid><description>The first in a series of podcasts bringing you doses of ravey bass music at the end of each month. In this episode I review 2014 in a flurry of 62 tunes from the past year in just under 2 hours. And it hasn&amp;rsquo;t been a bad year at all. PF 2015!​
Date: December 2014
Length: 1:52:28
Guest: none
Release of the month: none (this episode pre-dates this accidental cliché!)</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>http://www.masquerave.cz/pages/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.masquerave.cz/pages/about/</guid><description>The Masquerave Podcast is a regular podcast by Prague-based UK bass DJ and producer Z-Kat that aims to showcase the best new music from the bass scene.
Masquerave began as a monthly podcast in December 2014 in which Z-Kat played a mix of the hottest tunes of the last month, often accompanied by a guest mix or feature mix with a theme. Each podcast also featured a &amp;ldquo;release of the month&amp;rdquo; which celebrated the one EP or album from the last month&amp;rsquo;s selection which excelled the most in the now dying art of making a good release (as opposed to simply a collection of good tracks).</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>http://www.masquerave.cz/pages/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.masquerave.cz/pages/contact/</guid><description>We&amp;rsquo;d love to hear from you, especially if you&amp;rsquo;d like to submit a guest mix. To contact us, email zeibura@gmail.com
You can also report issues with the website on Github. This site is built using Hugo on Github Pages, using a theme based on Hugo Cards.</description></item></channel></rss>